# Eduardo Ayr Pereira Orsi Software Developer

■ duduayr@gmail.com

+55 47 99175-8354

https://github.com/Eduardo-Orsi

in https://www.linkedin.com/in/eduardo-orsi/

## **PROFILE**

Software developer with significant experience in web development and web scraping using Python. Strong technical skills in Django, Flask, FastAPI, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, as well as libraries such as requests, BeautifulSoup, Scrapy, and Selenium. Experienced in working with Docker, Docker-compose, NGINX, and cloud environments. Currently involved in a cutting-edge research project in the field of Artificial Intelligence, exploring Convolutional Neural Network (CNN) and Vision Transformer architectures for image analysis.

## PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

**Software Developer** 

Jul 2022 – Dec 2023

EDNA.CENTER - LGPD & Compliance

- In charge of strategic integrations between the consent management system and market platforms, driving compliance and efficiency.
- Led the identification and selection of systems for integration, as well as the creation and maintenance of essential APIs for daily operations.
- Responsible for the platform modernization using a robust technology stack: Django, Python, Selenium, and MySQL.

**Software Analyst** 

Sep 2020 – Jul 2022

Brazil

Brazil

EDNA.CENTER - LGPD & Compliance

- Key strategist in the configuration and optimization of the customer service CRM (Hubspot) and the WordPress platform, enhancing communication and operational
- Proactively engaged in the creation of web automation scripts, boosting productivity and the quality of internal processes.
- Effectively translated client demands into technical requirements, ensuring a software solution aligned with business needs.

## **EDUCATION**

**Computer Science** 

Feb 2021 – present

UNIVALI - Universidade do Vale do Itajaí

#### **SKILLS**

• Python

• Django

- Django Rest Framework
- Selenium

- Web Scrapping
- SQL

Pandas

• REST APIs

- Git
- Docker

NGINX

• Data Processing

## **PROJECTS**

#### **Shipping API for Ecommerce**

Developed with FastAPI and integrated with Kangu

## **Artstation Webscraper**

Project that retrieves all profiles from Artstation

#### **Talbots Law Webscraper**

Project that collects data on British lawyers site

#### **Data Consent Web Application**

Web app to collect data consent (EDNA.CENTER)

## LANGUAGES